[Music]
[Música]
Now come on my kids how are you all
ahora pasa mi chavalería como estáis
good welcome one more day to my channel it's
buenos bienvenidos un día más a mi canal
been a while since I recorded a video I have
que hacía tiempo que no grababa un vídeo
n't uploaded something that well actually yes I did
no subía algo que bueno en realidad sí
until yesterday I uploaded this video
que subía hasta ayer subí este vídeo
everything happens happens and ximo from the
todo ocurra ocurra y ximo de los juegos
squid games and not me fitz I'm
del calamar y no lo me fitz estoy
preparing another one that is in the style of
preparando otro que por el estilo de
big brother and as long as
gran hermano y como no lo vaya a
nobody is going to pressure me who says look at my
presionar nadie que diga mira mi
philosophy and I'm going to earn money I will do it
filosofía y voy a ganar dinero lo hago
but if there are no visits babe in between take
pero si no hay visitas nena de por medio
advantage of this idea that I always
provecho así esta idea que yo siempre me
take a nap of things always bunk from
duermo la siesta de cosas siempre litera
12 in the morning to 4 in the afternoon the
el 12 de la mañana a las 4 de la tarde
whole hour is good to sleep
toda la hora es buena para dormir
sit also make it so
asiento también me lo pongáis así de
easy for me I'm crazy I'm crazy because we've
fácil estoy rayado estoy rayado porque
been quite stagnant all month
llevamos todo el mes la verdad bastante
until very good the least I
estancado hasta muy bueno el menos me
can complain the truth is that all the
puedo quejar la verdad que todos los
channels have done very well they have grown a
canales han ido muy bien han crecido
lot but this channel the main channel
mucho pero este canal el canal principal
is quite stagnant it was looted and
está bastante estancado está saqueaba y
at 417 and it's giving me all that number it
en 417 y me está dando todos ese número
's giving me all and it's that me or the
me está dando todos y es que yo o la
kids had it easier no  I
chavalería lo tenía más fácil no a los
do four stupid things to the kids and
chavales le hago cuatro tonterías y se
everyone subscribes I don't promise them
suscriben todo el mundo no les prometo
anything and they subscribe it's just that I hurt
cualquier cosa y se suscriben es que yo
the gentleman I don't know what to do I get
al señor hería no sé qué hacerle yo a
up to the kids I start
los chavales me levanto me pongo a
hitting the chair and they
pegarle por raso a la silla y se
really subscribe ma'am or so that's how it is
suscriben de verdad señora o sea eso es
welcome to youtube on youtube there's
así bienvenidas a youtube en youtube hay
crazy people here you can freak out I get up
acá loco que podéis flipar yo me levanto
and start hitting the chair and the
y empiezo a pegarle a la silla y los
kids subscribe these are things that
chavales se suscriben son cosas que
happen I don't understand but I'm with your
pasan no lo entiendo pero yo con la
honor for I don't know what you're doing
señoría por no sé qué es lo que hace
because the other day I posted a
porque el otro día puse un meme de los
simple meme of the baby that is burning and your
simples del bebé que se quema y la
honor gets offended you say that it's not
señoría se ofenden se ofende dice que no
right how can I be happy that
está bien que como puedo alegrarme de
a baby is burning ma'am it's a
que se queme un bebé señora que es un
meme 12 years with you what I'm going to
meme 12 años con ustedes lo que voy a
do is clean the chair that we are
hacer es limpiar la silla que estamos
subscribe to see cleaning well
suscribiros para ver limpieza bueno
family this is going to be a video in which I'm
familia este va a ser un vídeo en el que
going to go to the nougat I'm going to this thing it
voy a ir al turrón voy a esta cosa
was really a little detached this
realmente estaba un poco despegado este
I wasn't paying much attention to the topic so it's true that I was seeing a lot of action on Twitter these days but it's busy with other things and the truth is that this topic is being neglected but it's crazy it turns out about these days there had been a lot of clicks on Sálvame in which they are chasing Jules
en el que van persiguiendo a jules
Janeiro who is the daughter of Jesulín de
janeiro que es la hija de jesulín de
Ubrique and María José Campanario they are
ubrique y de maría josé campanario van
chasing her but in a very
persiguiendo la pero en plan o sea muy
arch plan I mean in the program you see how
arco o sea en el programa se ve como
Jules leaves her house you are 18
jules sale de su casa your tiene 18
years old and you have become independent and you are
añitos y se ha independizado y está
living in Madrid you are not living with
viviendo en madrid no está viviendo con
your parents I think you are living with
sus padres creo que está viviendo con
some friends but it's crazy because they
unas amigas pero es que flipa porque que
show where she lives anyone who
muestran dónde vive cualquiera que
knows the street or who searches
conozca la calle o que se ponga a buscar
on Google + can find where
en el google + puede localizar dónde
the kid lives I mean this is super
vive la chaval o sea esto es súper
dangerous and I'm freaking out because in
peligroso y yo flipo porque es que en
this type of program they don't hold back
este tipo de programa no se cortan un
this is very serious we
pelo nace esto es muy grave nosotros
here youtubers are always very
aquí los youtubers siempre tenemos mucho
careful that our
cuidado que se infinite nuestra
address our phone number our
dirección nuestro teléfono nuestras
things and these people who  they wait at the
cosas y esta gente que te esperan en la
door of the house to record anyone can
puerta de casa de graba cualquiera puede
know where she lives or rather for almost ten
saber dónde vive o sea durante casi diez
minutes you watch they start chasing her down
minutos te reloj la van persiguiendo por
the street and they cross several blocks it's
la calle y se cruzan varias manzanas es
worth it from
que vale
far away and the girl is not
a lejísimo y esta la chavala sin
answering them and the reporter is
responderles y la reportera de
transmitting the microphone in her face
transmitiendo el micrófono en la cara
sticking the cell phone camera in her face a couple of times
metiéndole un par de veces la cámara
to see what you
para el móvil para ver que lo que
were getting off I'm hallucinating I'm hallucinating the
estabas apeando yo alucino alucino la
only time the girl turns around
única vez que la chavala se da la vuelta
after like 3 or 4 minutes and answers
ya como a los 3 o 4 minutos y contesta
something it's to tell her the following would you
algo es para decirle lo siguiente te
like to say anything there are some right now
gustaría decir nada hay unos ahora mismo
that we are live that have the
que estamos en directo que tienes el
microphone open on Sálvame to say
micrófono de sálvame abierto para decir
everything you want that feminism you
todo lo que tú quieras que el feminismo
use it whenever you want okay boom
lo usáis cuándo queréis vale zasca
literally boom in the mouth this clip had been
literalmente zasca en la boca este clip
made a lot both on
se había realizado mucho tanto en
twitter and on you as on all the
twitter como en ti como en todas las
social networks and this gets to the
redes sociales y esto le llega a la
potato Carlota corredera I want to
patata a carlota corredera que quiero
know what she means
saber a qué se refiere
what do you mean Carlota starts
a qué te refieres a carlota empieza a
sending questions to the reporter what does she
mandarle preguntas a la reportera a qué
mean by feminism  what she
se refiere con el feminismo a qué se
means as if feminism were hers
refiere como si el feminismo fuera de
it's as if she were the owner
ella es como si ella fuera la dueña
expert in feminism that you can't
experta en feminismo que no se le puede
refute anything they keep chasing them for
refutar nada las siguen persiguiendo
like ten minutes okay after that and
como diez minutos vale después de eso y
how offended she feels because they have
cómo se siente muy ofendida porque han
damaged her feminist ego she sends her the
dañado su ego feminista le manda el
following message
siguiente mensaje
they are here here here I want to go
están aquí aquí aquí yo quiero dirigirme
to
a
work a message
trabajar un mensaje
that I didn't feel what the [ __ ] did she believe when
que no sentía que se creyó cuando
you want we can really meet and I'll really explain to you
quieras de verdad quedamos y te explico
what feminism is because
de verdad lo que es el feminismo porque
maybe you don't know it and hey it's okay
igual no lo igual no lo sabes y oye no
we're all in a
pasa nada estamos todos en proceso de
learning process and one has a
aprendizaje y uno tiene un proceso de
learning process none Carlota Corredera and
aprendizaje ninguno carlota corredera y
I have my own thoughts and I think what
yo tengo mi propio pensamiento y pienso
comes to mind if you
lo que me sale de los mismísimos si
want I'll send you another message Carlota
quieres te mando yo otro mensaje carlota
Corredera unblock me and I'll
corredera quítame el bloqueo y yo te
explain to you why you are a
explico a ti porque eres una feminista
selective feminist and why your feminism is disgusting
selectiva y porque tu feminismo da asco
and why your feminism is a lie
y porque tu feminismo mente mentira
your feminism is a fool's game that you
vuestro feminismo es un papelón que
have acquired to use as a
habéis adquirido para utilizarlo como
weapon against whoever interests you it
arma contra quien ustedes interesa
's simply and plainly an
simple y llanamente es un argumento
easy argument and in fact  Carlota I challenge you to
fácil y de hecho carlota te reto a
debate in the forum of your choice, be it
debatir en el foro que tú quieras ya sea
my channel, yours, or wherever you want to remove
mi canal el tuyo o donde quiera quitar
the block, and I will explain to you what
el bloqueo y yo te explico a ti lo que
the presumption of innocence is if you have
es la presunción de inocencia si tienes
any questions because we are all learning
alguna duda que todo estamos aprendiendo
from what I see because regarding the
por lo que veo porque sobre la
presumption of innocence, violation of
presunción de inocencia vulneración de
human rights, okay because you have
los derechos humanos vale porque tenéis
several convictions for violating the right to
varias condenas de vulnerar derecho a la
privacy and you have several convictions for
intimidad y tenéis varias condenadas por
violating the right to the honor of the lord, okay
vulnerar derecho al honor del señor vale
if Carlota wants, call me, remove the
si quiere carlota llama me quitan el
block, it ends up in an echo chamber
bloqueo se acaba en una cámara de eco
that I debate with you and I will explain everything
que yo debato contigo y te explico todo
you want because I am not 18
lo que tú quieras que yo no tengo 18
years old, I am 36 but I talk to you, I
años tengo 36 pero yo hablo contigo yo
have no problem talking to
no tengo ningún problema en hablar
you wherever you want it turns out that
contigo donde quieras resulta ser que
since this girl turned 18
desde que esta chica cumplió los 18 años
and simply because of that for having turned 18, for having
y simplemente por eso por haber cumplido
made the very serious mistake of
por haber cometido el gravísimo error de
turning 18, these people have been
cumplir 18 años esta gente llevan
chasing them down the street every
persiguiéndolas por la calle todos los
day and making fun of her it is
días y burlándose de ella es
completely regrettable, he
completamente lamentable él
has a white iPhone, he has everything cool, pay
tiene un iphone white tiene todo guay
attention now, the one who  comes around here she did
atentos ahora la que viene por aquí
n't study but naturally she didn't study
no estudió pero naturalmente no estudió
but there's no need for this because they've been making
pero no hace falta esto porque llevan
fun of each other for months that
todos estos meses cachón dándose de que
the girl isn't studying at the
la chavala no esté estudiando en estos
moment and has everything it's completely
momento y tenga de todo es completamente
embarrassing to see a group of people in their
vergonzoso ver un grupo de personas de
60s, between 50 and 60 years old,
60 años de entre 50 y 60 años estar
making fun of something versus
cachondeándose alguna cosa contra
gossip one thing is to talk about the heart
cotilleo una cosa es hablar del corazón
and another thing is to play the ceo and another very
y otra cosa haces al ceo y otra cosa muy
big thing is a group of people between
grande es un grupo de personas de entre
50 and 60 years old making fun
50 y 60 años cachondeándose en prime
of an
time en máxima audiencia de una niña de
18 year old girl in prime time, making fun of the
18 años burlándose todo el tiempo la
idle life of Julia Janeiro in Madrid all the time we're in Madrid
vida ociosa de julia janeiro en madrid
we could already live off the story she
estamos ya podría vivir del cuento
studies she works she doesn't study or work what does
estudia trabaja ni estudia ni trabaja
Jules do and they start to wonder
que hace jules y se ponen a preguntarse
what she supports herself with she has a father
qué de qué se mantiene tiene un padre
who is a millionaire she has a father who
que es millonario tiene un padre que
apart from having been a star in
aparte de haber sido una estrella en el
bullfighting comes with like I don't know how many gas stations he has I don't
toreo viene como no sé cuánta gasolinera
know how many businesses he has I don't know
tiene no sé cuántos negocios tiene no sé
how much land he has money to spare or rather
cuántos terreno le sobra el dinero o sea
I think that when he doesn't have a towel at
yo creo que cuando no tiene la toalla a
hand he dries himself when he gets out of the shower with
mano se seca cuando sale de la ducha con
500 if he feels like
billetes de 500 si se le antoja tener a
spoiling the girl he can do whatever he
la niña consentida puede hacer lo que
wants some parents think it is the
quiera algunos padres nos parece la
best you may think it is worse each one
mejor te puede parecer peor cada uno
educates their children with the values ​​they
educa a sus hijos con los valores que
want but it is legitimate study work what are you
quiera pero es lícito estudia trabaja
doing are you preparing for what are you
que está haciendo se está preparando a
going to do what do you do
que se va a dedicar a que os dedicáis
Rafa Mora you who are Rafa Mora
usted de rafa mora tú que eres rafa mora
literally you who are you are a
literalmente tú que eres eres un
contestant of 'women men and
concursante de 'mujeres hombres y
vice versa' what are you who are there
viceversa' que sois lo que estáis ahí
what the hell am I because if you take away this
qué soy porque si quitan está
Rafa Mora and some
rafa mora y algunos concursantes de
reality contestants some of you who are there
reality algunos de los que estáis ahí
surely have had years of
seguramente hayáis tenido años de
career even years of study but
carrera incluso años de estudio pero
well in the end you are what I tell you a
bueno al final sois lo que os digo un
group of people between 50 and 60 years old
grupo de personas de entre 50 y 60 años
who are sitting in 'prime time'
que estáis sentados en 'prime time'
humiliating an 18 year old girl here she
humillando a una niña de 18 años aquí
is commenting on the fact that the
anda está comentando el hecho de que la
girl has had breast surgery and in the
chavala se haya operado el pecho y es al
end it may be news of the gossip
final pues puede ser noticia del corazón
press totally legitimate but there are
prensa rosa totalmente lícito pero hay
some other programs like for example
algunos otros programas como por ejemplo
this one in which you brought JCE to  a
en éste en el que trajiste jce a una
friend we're talking about just
amiga os estamos hablando de recién
turned 18 they brought an ex friend who
cumplidos 18 trajeron a una ex amiga que
called the program to tell
se dedicó a llamar al programa a contar
how much god it cost Jules that
con cuántos dios había costado jules que
if now she was with someone who's been with her for a
si ahora estaba con uno que se hace un
couple of years she's going with someone else but it
par de años está van con otro pero es
turns out that the girl has had a boyfriend
que resultase que la chavala tiene novio
for years or two years you're
desde hace años o dos años me estás
telling me who that
contando con quien se ha costado esa
girl has gone through with being a minor now and she gets stuck with a bunch
niña siendo menor ya y se pega una panda
of boomers between 50 and 60 years old I repeat
de boomers de entre 50 y 60 años repito
and judging a girl who has
y juzgando a una chavala que si se ha
slept with whoever she had to
enrollado con quien se haya tenido que
sleep with in her adolescence is
enrollar en su adolescencia es
mind-blowing and that's what I'm telling you I mean at the
alucinante y es lo que os digo o sea al
end of the day the fact that you are a
fin y al cabo el hecho de que tú seas un
public figure not being the daughter of
personaje público no ser la hija de
someone is good the only thing that
quien es bueno a lo único que se agarra
this is holding on to more thank you very much because she already has
esto más muchas gracias porque ya tiene
a sister she has a sister who
una hermana ella tiene una hermana que
is the daughter of Belén Esteban okay
es la hija de belén esteban vale
collaborator of the program who is
colaboradora del programa que está
commenting on all this content with
comentando todos estos contenidos con
them no by the way the day they make
ellos no que por cierto el día que hagan
a documentary about Belén Esteban about Belén
un documental de belén esteban de belén
Esteban and Jesulín de Ubrique after
esteban y jesulín de ubrique después de
what they have  made with antonio david
lo que han hecho con antonio david
flores belenes esteban is going to be at the
flores belenes esteban va a quedar a la
height of the beloved's bitumen commenting on
altura del betún del amado comentando en
the results videos she is close and they
los vídeos de resultados cerca está y la
respect her she turned 18
respetan está cumplió 18 años el año
last year or the year before two or three
pasado o la anterior hace ya dos o tres
years ago okay she turned 18 but she did not know how to
años vale cumplió 18 años pero no supo
assimilate the repercussions that people
asimilar la repercusión que la gente se
messed with her this thing that is
metía con ella esta cosa que está en
her right because she decided to put her
todo su derecho pues decidió poner sus
networks in private and asked in a
redes en privadas y pidió en un
statement respect that she did not want to
comunicado respeto que ella no quería
be a public figure and that she did not want to
ser personaje público y que no quería
dedicate herself to anything popular because the only
dedicarse a nada popular pues la única
difference there is with jules who is her
diferencia que hay con jules que es su
sister on her father's side is that the
hermana por parte de padre es que la
girl has the instagram in public I
chavala tiene el instagram en público o
mean literally I have been watching
sea literalmente me he estado viendo
all the programs that they have made for the
todo lo programa que le han hecho a la
girl and the girl from what it seems
chavala y la chavala por lo que se ve
until today that it is not known if it
hasta el día de hoy que no se sabe si
will change later but until
cambiará más adelante pero hasta el día
today since six months ago that she
de hoy desde hace ya seis meses que
came of age the girl does not
cumplió la mayoría de edad la chavala no
stop repeating that she does not want to
para de repetir que ella no quiere
dedicate herself to the media or anything like that that she
dedicarse a los medios ni nada por el
has her instagram and she does
estilo que tiene su instagram y casa
some campaign on instagram but that she does not
alguna campaña en instagram pero que no
want  dedicate to the media then
se quiere dedicar a los medios entonces
what happens because it is legal the
qué es lo que pasa porque es legal el
lawful of a public figure has their
lícito de un personaje público tiene sus
networks in public in the daughter of that neri they
redes en público en la hija de que neri
are chasing her down the street without
la van persiguiendo por la calle sin
any kind of respect you know or rather
ningún tipo de respeto ya sabéis o sea
I do heart I also do
yo hago corazón también lo hago
gossip and I do salt she had an operation a few
cotilleos y hago sal se operó unas
lines no I mean there is nothing that's it well he
líneas no o sea que no hay nada ya está
respects her because she is the daughter of
pues la respeta porque es la hija de
belén esteban the daughter of the same father
belén esteban la hija del mismo padre
but since she is the daughter of belén esteban
pero como es la hija de belén esteban
one of the star collaborators of
una de las colaboradoras estrellas de
telecinco time she does respect her the
telecinco vez a ésta si la respeta la
question is that carlota corredera is
cuestión es que carlota corredera está
very offended she is very offended by the
muy ofendida está muy ofendida por lo de
selective feminist thing that she says that they
feminista selectiva que dice que se lo
tell her a lot entangle us in this
dicen mucho enrede nosotros en este
program we have not used
programa no hemos utilizado que yo sepa
feminism in a selective way as far as I know which is
el feminismo de manera selectiva que es
something that is also usually said about us
algo que también suele decir de nosotros
that some women yes to others no that is not
que algunas mujeres sí a otras no eso no
true in any case I have
es verdad en cualquier caso tengo
saying murderers even if they are women
diciendo asesinas aunque sean mujeres
literally carlota corredera when I
literalmente carlota corredera cuando
worked broadcasting the documentary by
trabaje emitiendo el documental de
antonio david flores well de rociíto
antonio david flores bueno de rociíto
but whose protagonist of so much of david
pero cuyo protagonista de tanto de david
flores literally you took out no  Save me,
flores literalmente sacaste ningún
dedicate an
sálvame dedícate un sálvame una tarde
entire afternoon to yourself because by unfortunate
entera porque dio la desgraciada
coincidence the body of one
casualidad que apareció el cuerpo de una
of the Tenerife lines appeared, not that her
de las líneas de tenerife no que su
father had murdered her, there's no way
padre la había asesinado no hay como
you have the terms for these
tenéis los términos de estos violencia
vicarious violence to define what a son
vicaria para definir a lo que es un hijo
of the great boom is, being miserable that
de la gran boom ser miserable que no
people like that shouldn't exist in
tiene que existir personas como esa en
the world, they should be locked up
el mundo que tienen que estar encerradas
for life at the very least, but hey, you
de por vida como mínimo pero bueno
made a program, you dedicated
ustedes hicisteis un programa dedicaste
an entire afternoon, which is neither a
es una tarde entera que eso no es ni
tribute nor anything, to talk about the case of the
homenaje ni nada a hablar del caso de el
murder by the father of that
asesinato por parte del padre de esa
girl, you could almost say that during
niña casi se podría decir que durante
the entire afternoon in that program that you
toda la tarde en ese programa que le
dedicated to her, girl, the girl had a half
dedica chica la niña tenía es una medio
smile on her face, almost, and well, being
sonrisa en la cara como casi y bueno
able to use our
pudiendo utilizar nuestro vuestro
selective feminism to compare
feminismo selectivo para comparar a
Antonio David and defame him and call them
antonio david y difamar lo y llamarlos
even more mistreating, they grabbed the
más todavía maltratar a agarraron al
argument that look, there are parents who
argumento de que mira hay padres que
murder their children and commit
asesinan a sus hijos y hacen la
vicarious violence, not incredibly
violencia vicaria no increíblemente
disgusting and incredibly disgusting that you
asqueroso e increíblemente asqueroso que
use six girls murdered by
utiliza seis a unas niñas asesinadas por
their father for your defamation, Antonio
su padre para vuestra difamación antonio
Davis, to play ball  rice that now we
davis para pelotear arrocito que ahora
will go to it without leaving aside of
iremos a ello sin dejar de lado por
course with the seriousness that treated the
supuesto con la seriedad que tratase el
subject
tema
instead and the great one
en cambio y el grande
today
hoy
literally said a phrase like
literalmente ha dicho una frase en plan
we are not talking about any crime he
de no estamos hablando de un crimen
has nothing to say what's wrong family I
no tiene algo que decir qué pasa familia
have to dodge the 12,000 euros
tengo que sortear los 12.000 euros
save me lemon or save me orange and you know
sálvame limón o sálvame naranja y sabes
what I'm going to remind you Carlota Corredera
que te voy a recordar carlota corredera
that exactly five or six days
que justamente cinco o seis días antes
before this happened with the
de que pasara esto con las líneas de
Tenerife lines a girl from Sant Joan Despí was
tenerife una niña de sant joan despí fue
tuned by one of her parents but
afinada por uno de sus progenitores pero
you know why you don't
sabéis por qué no le dediquéis ni
even dedicate a minute to it on your [ __ ]
siquiera un minuto en vuestro
program because it was nothing at the hands of
programa porque fue us nada por manos de
the mother to get revenge on the father that
la madre para vengarse del padre ese
your disgusting feminism has in fact
vuestro asqueroso feminismo de hecho ha
done what you are doing with Yul
hecho que estáis haciendo con yul
Janeiro it could not be called harassment because it is not
janeiro no se podría llamar acoso porque
something illegal she is not a
no es algo ilegal no es un personaje
public figure no but what you are doing
público no pero esto que estáis haciendo
dedicating guides to them and Díaz to talk about
dedicándoles guías y díaz a hablar de
her to say bad things making fun of them
ella a decir cosas malas hacerles burlas
and all these things telling things about her
y todas estas cosas contar cosas de su
life and so on a few  months
vida y demás hace unos meses
referring to the still you have
refiriéndose al todavía lo habéis
called it abuse this same thing that I am
llamado maltrato esto mismo que estoy
doing with Jules months ago if we were
haciendo con jules hace meses si nos
referring to Antonio Avila they were
referíamos antonio ávila lo estaban
calling it abuse in exchange for Rocío
llamando maltrato a cambio de que rocío
Carrasco who had sued up to her
carrasco que tenía demandados hasta las
eyebrows she and her husband will withdraw the
cejas ella y su marido os retirará las
lawsuits that then you have lost the
demandas que luego habéis perdido la
lawsuit Antonio Davis commends and
demanda compulsa antonio davis y han
the agreements that you have with them have come to light in the sentence so that they would
salido a la luz en la sentencia los
withdraw the lawsuit in exchange for what if it
retirasen la demanda a cambio de qué si
is the role of your feminism it is
es el papel de vuestro feminismo es el
selective feminism Carlota Cordera in
feminismo selectivo carlota cordera de
fact I have a folder account here
hecho tengo aquí una cuenta carpetita
that she took at random it is worth pointing out
que cogió al azhar vale para señalarte
your selective feminism again and how it
otra vez tu feminismo selectivo y como
defends some women and you get to her
defiende a unas mujeres y llegas a ella
sane so that they withdraw the lawsuits
cuerdo para que os retiren las demandas
and others if not you have been for the
y a otras sino no habéis estado durante
entire last week calling a cuckold
toda la última semana llamando cornuda
not revealing here some supposed
no desvelando aquí unos supuestos
horns that they have put on Irene
cuernos que le han puesto a irene
Rosales that seem to make you happy because it
rosales que parece que os alegran porque
has contained you that a woman is cheated on
os ha contenido que a una mujer le
but oh well it is well
pongan los cuernos pero bueno bien es
gossip is not news not here with
cotilleo no es noticia no aquí con
riberas a public figure they record them in
riberas un personaje público las graban
a nightclub according to you in the end it
una discoteca según ustedes al final
turns out that it was not that he was
resulta ser que no era que le estuviera
cheating on her airen he was with
poniendo los cuernos airén es estaba con
the wife of one of his friends but well
la mujer de uno de sus amigos pero bueno
look how you give the news they watch us
mira como dais la noticia nos miran
put the news doing a
poner la noticia haciendo aquí una
documentary parody here with a deer not clear
parodia documental con ciervo no claro
because a woman with horns is a symbol
porque una mujer con cuernos es símbolo
of parodying her there is no need to joke around
de hacerle parodia no hay cachondearse
here a room with horns in fact let's see let
aquí una sala con cuernos de hecho a ver
's listen to what our
vamos a escuchar que dice tener nuestra
partner terelu says she has let's see what
compañera terelu vamos a ver qué es lo
tele lugo says while she collaborates
que dice tele lugo mientras que colabora
on the island of temptation evil
en la isla de la tentación malvada
but
pero
being evil I would like there to be weight
siendo malvada me gustaría que haya peso
or rather she would love for a contestant
o sea le encantaría que una concursante
from the island of temptation to be
de la isla de las tentaciones les fueran
unfaithful to them to be humiliated on the
infiel que fuera humillada en el
program she would like being evil
programa le gustaría siendo malvada
well the campos folder what a
bueno la carpeta de las campos que una
gem
joyita
this was on the program viva la vida we
esto fue en el programa de viva la vida
commented on it on the secondary channel and
lo comentamos en el canal secundario y
in the news it is not supposed to be
en las noticias no esté se supone que es
a comedian but to me it seems more
un humorista pero a mí me parece más
like a clown literally a clown
bien un payaso literalmente un payaso
that has it the typical one that wants to be
que lo tiene el típico que se quiere
funny by balls and  it's no
hacer gracioso por y no tiene
joke because the bull is worth it if they have him
gracias pues el torito vale si lo tienen
there so he does things that are no
ahí puesto para que haga cosas que no
jokes and one of the jokes he did
tiene gracias y una de las gracias que
was grab the aunt we are
le dio por hacer fue a la tía
the oldest who is here behind
estamos el mayor que está aquí atrás
okay and shake her and then the niece
vale y zarandearla y luego la sobrina
look look at the humiliation you can see
mira mirar la humillación ese se le ven
the fraga the girl grabs her he shakes her he
la fraga a la chavala la coge la
drops the microphone and they show the
zarandea se le cae micrófono y dan la
girl's face look look look at
cara de la chavala es mirad mirad mirad
the girl's face how bad it is for her to
la cara de la chavala lo mal que lo pasa
look at his face in anguish the
de mirarle a la cara de angustia la
girl runs away from the set but
chavala sale huyendo del plato pero
then comes back laughing and forgives him and
luego vuelve entre risas y lo perdona y
against this guy there is no kind of
contra este tío no hay ningún tipo de
retaliation for that humiliation nobody no matter how
represalia por esa humillación nadie por
much you want to be funny has to
mucho que te quiera ser gracioso tiene
invade anyone's physical space and much
que invadir el espacio físico de nadie y
less to grab him and shake her okay
menos para cogerlo y zarandearla vale
but oh well I envy her the girl puts her
pero bueno la envidio la chavala se mete
hands between her legs gets up and
las manos entre las piernas se levanta y
leaves the set laughing
sale riendo avergonzada del plato
embarrassed with a face of anguish that
angustiada con una cara de angustia que
gave me the creeps but oh well since
me dio cosa hasta a mí pero bueno como
this girl has neither job nor
esta chavala no tiene ni oficio ni
benefit  the daughter of the 1 and she has to
beneficio que la hija del 1 y tiene que
be collaborating and has nothing else to
estar colaborando y no tiene otra cosa
do if she wants to work on
que hacer si quiere trabajar en
Telecinco Rajoy stayed on the program
telecinco rajoy se quedó en el programa
okay he endured the storm and stayed on
vale aguantó el chaparrón y se quedó en
the program this guy had no
el programa que este tío no tenía ningún
kind of retaliation or big dismissal or anything like that
tipo de represalia ni gran despedido ni
pay attention to these
nada por el estilo atentos a estas
words of having a field the other day
palabras de tener un campo el otro día
on Viva la Vida because they were
en viva la vida porque fueron
wonderful and they are silent goddesses
maravillosas y se diosas calladas
I separated from me and my son like that I
me separé de mí de mi hijo así yo los
want to see them if I want to be with him there is no
quiero ver si yo quiero estar con él no
reason to look at you I can not
hay no existe motivo mirarte puedo no
see the father play yourselves this
ver al padre jugar ustedes mismo esta
phrase here we have the sálvame that they
frase aquí tenemos el sálvame que
publish some private audios of this
publican unos audios privados de esta
girl Alejandra Rubio the daughter of Terelu they
chica alejandra rubio la hija de terelu
publish all over the face some
publican por toda la cara unos audios
private audios that are all good these
privados que es todo bueno estos
constitute a crime to publish
constitutivos de delito para publicar
audios of third parties in which you are not a
audios de terceros en los que no eres
participant it is by criminal means what he
partícipe es por la vía penal esto que
puts to see he is telling you and Matamoros
pone a ver te está contando y matamoros
calling something serious to the daughter of Kiko
llamando algo grave a la hija de kiko
Matamoros he is calling her a [ __ ] or a
matamoros le está llamando como o
[ __ ] or something like that
como o alguna cosa por el estilo
okay that we are and you see yourself with the ones in
vale eso estamos y te ves con las de
spirit  from tango you take them with the insulted
ánimo de tango los llevas con la insultó
Anna Matamoros Carlota Estar was showing off
de anna matamoros carlota estar estuvo
her selective feminism
haciendo gala de su feminismo selectivo
in a trial in which the
en un juicio en el que condenaron a las
television factories were convicted of insulting for
fábricas de la tele por insultar durante
weeks on several of your programs
semanas en varios de vuestro programa a
a woman named Pepa Jiménez who
una mujer que se llama jiménez que
is a journalist we are going to listen to see
es periodista nos vamos a escuchar a ver
what she says in court
qué dice en el juicio
to Mrs. Jiménez daughter of a [ __ ] of pus
a la señora jiménez hija de de pus
shameless bad person mafia true
sinvergüenza mala persona mafiosa verdad
or trash unfortunate with cross bad
o basura desgraciada con cruza mala
professional to take for a sack this woman did not
profesional a tomar por saco esta tía no
occur to them to put an end to this feast
se les ocurrió poner fin a este festín
of insults always directly in the
de insultos siempre directamente en el
program introducing it in the
programa introduciéndolo en los
following ones that continued doing it
siguientes que continuaron haciéndolo
Carlota true at this time was the
carlota verdadera en esta época era la
director of Salvador de consulta that
directora de salvador de consultar que
right now
ahora mismo
what would it be that the while does not remember
qué sería lo que el rato no se acuerda
go what was happening here with your sonority
vaya qué pasaba aquí con tu sonoridad
sister what was happening here with your sorority
hermana qué pasaba aquí con tu sororidad
this is one of the collaborators that you
este es uno de los colaboradores que
currently have in several of our
tenéis actualmente en varios de nuestros
programs we are going to see what it is
programas vamos a ver qué es lo que
statements until the ECB but they are
declaraciones hasta que el bce pero son
personal if you make me understand one
personales si tú me das a entender una
thing and I accelerate okay then I do not
cosa y yo me acelero vale luego no me
say up to here load I'm not leaving as you
digas hasta aquí carga no me voy como
all know we have been watching in the
todos sabréis hemos estado viendo en los
last few months during all the videos
últimos meses durante todos los vídeos
that I have made analyzing the documentary
que he hecho analizando el documental
above all I could be here for hours and
sobre todo podría estar aquí horas y
hours and hours taking out libraries taking out
horas y horas sacando bibliotecas
compilations of how Telecinco does
sacando recopilaciones de como telecinco
not behave in a very
no se comporta de una manera muy
feminist way precisely for me all this is
feminista precisamente para mí todo esto
not that important either or
tampoco que tenga mucha importancia o
all the clicks that we are seeing
sea todos los clic que estamos viendo
are not super serious or two
tampoco como que sean súper graves o dos
shows and the people who
espectáculos y las personas que se
project this type of content because in the
proyectan este tipo de contenidos por al
end everyone does a bit the same here
final todos hace un poco lo mismo aquí
the problem comes when
el problema viene cuando en algunas
sometimes you are interested in being extremely
ocasiones te interesa ser extremadamente
feminist having tremendous security you
feminista tener una seguridad tremenda
condemn all kinds of attacks on
condenas todo tipo de ataques a las
women but when you are
mujeres pero cuando te interesan
only interested but yes it is true that to
solamente pero sí que es verdad que para
finish with this video I am going to touch on
finalizar con este vídeo voy a tocar el
Telecinco's Achilles heel the issue
talón de aquiles de telecinco el tema
that it has
que tiene
in the corridors of Telecinco well not in
en los pasillos de telecinco bueno no en
the corridors but talking about it in broadcasts in
los pasillos sino hablar en emisiones en
any broadcast of Telecinco
cualquier emisión de telecinco no se
this issue is not talked about it is the taboo issue and it is
habla de este tema es el tema taboo y es
the issue of Carlota Grado Carlota Prado
el tema de carlota grado carlota prado
was a girl who was allegedly
fue una chica que fue presuntamente
raped in the Big Brother house in the
violada en la casa de gran hermano en la
last edition that had to be broadcast
última edición que se tuvo que emitir
because  after this happened and there is
porque después de que pasara esto y haya
a pending complaint that is still
una denuncia pendiente que todavía a día
being prosecuted to this day because they have not been
de hoy está judicializada pues no han
able to broadcast Big Brother again in
podido volver a emitir granhermano de
fact they are no longer getting involved in Big
hecho ya no se está metiendo en el gran
Brother VIP they are broadcasting
hermano vip se está emitiendo ciclos
historical cycles like Big Brother but
histórico que gran hermano pero
disguised because advertisers do not
disfrazado porque los anunciantes no
want to advertise in this until it
quieren anunciarse en esto hasta que no
is clear here what is happening
sea claro aquí que lo que está pasando
Carlota Prado was allegedly raped
carlota prado fue presuntamente violada
inside the Big Brother house and no
dentro de la casa de gran hermano y no
one went to help her no one interrupted
fue nadie a socorrer nadie interrumpió
the broadcast of the program and no one entered
la emisión del programa y nadie entró
the house you know that the
dentro de la casa ya sabéis que la casa
Big Brother house is a reality show that is
de gran hermano es un reality en el que
broadcast live 24 hours a day it is not
se emite en directo 24 horas no está
monitored 24 hours a day by cameras as
vigilada 24 horas con cámara como viven
a series of people live inside the house
una serie de personas dentro de la casa
things happen and a girl was
pasan cosas y una chica fue
allegedly raped she said allegedly so
presuntamente violada dijo presuntamente
many times that I am a denialist what we
tantas veces que soy negacionista lo que
could say is almost that there is no
podríamos decir casi que casi que no hay
alleged and that in truth
presunto y que en verdad
apart from kicking out the contestant the
aparte de echar al concursante al
alleged rapist they would screw up or expel what is
presunto violador joderían o expulsar lo
least it is true that they released
que menos sí que es verdad que lanzaron
a series of statements and tried to
una serie de comunicados e intentaron
be more or less empathetic with the  the victim
ser más o menos empáticos con la víctima
went to the civil guard to report it
fueron a la guardia civil a denunciar
because it was their obligation basically
porque era su obligación básicamente
but they handled it like [ __ ]
pero lo gestionaron como el culo
they interrupted inside the house so
interrumpieron dentro de la casa para
that what was happening wouldn't happen and they didn't
que no pasase lo que estaba pasando ni
know how to handle the situation well they
supieron gestionar bien la situación en
locked the girl in the
encerraron a la chica en el
Big Brother confessional they
confesionario del gran hermano le
showed her own images of how
pusieron sus propias imágenes de cómo
the girl was allegedly being raped
estaba siendo presuntamente violada la
and that she was going to have a heart attack imagine
chica y que le iba a dar algo imagínate
the situation without any company from a
la situación sin ninguna compañía de un
family member a psychologist no no problem and
familiar un psicólogo no no hay pedo y
then the girl continued competing in the
luego la chica siguió concursando en el
brother and well yes it is true that I
hermano y bueno sí que es verdad que yo
commented a lot on this issue that it is not that
comentaba mucho de este tema que no es
really at the time they will try to
que realmente en su momento se intentará
silence it completely because yes that
silenciar del todo porque sí que ese
son more or less what had happened
hijo más o menos lo que había pasado
girl inside the house also
chica dentro de la casa también se lo
explained it to her colleagues and so on but
explico a los compañeros y demás pero a
today as the prosecutor's office is
día de hoy como la fiscalía le está
asking for types of sentences for these people
pidiendo tipo de condenas a esta gente
as part of the responsibility they do not
como parte de la responsabilidad no se
comment on the subject no I want to
pronuncian sobre el tema no yo quiero
know when Carlos chord right
saber cuando carlos acorde derecho
team to dedicate a program
equipo para dedicar un programa
exclusively to assume
exclusivamente a asumir
responsibility to ask for forgiveness for their
responsabilidades a pedir perdón por sus
mistakes clear mistakes we
errores claros errores cometemos
all make but this is a mistake of
cualquiera pero esto es un error de
these boys be to assume their mistakes
estos muchachos sea asumir sus errores
even compensate the girl because they
incluso indemnizar a la chica porque
are waiting to see if they are convicted or
están esperando a ver si les condena o
not to say that it was
no las condenas para decir es que
not our fault and it is like I
nosotros no tuvimos la culpa y es como
am not that feminist to make a program
no soy tan feminista hacer un programa
dedicate an entire program to ask for
dedicar un programa entero a pedir
forgiveness to rectify your mistake to
perdón a rectificar por vuestro error a
recognize and assume the mistake that
reconocer y asumir el error que
you made to give visibility to what
cometiste a dar visibilidad a lo que
happened if necessary why not compensate
pasó si hace falta por qué no indemnizar
the girls I mean are you waiting to
a las chicas o sea estáis esperando a
see if they hide to compensate them or I am a
ver si esconden a indemnizarlas o soy
feminist it does not fix there are many things
feminista no arregla hay muchas cosas
with agreements and with money from Nice I already
con acuerdos y con dinero de niza ya os
tell you a taboo subject that is not
digo un tema tabú del que no se
spoken about and today in any
pronuncia y a día de hoy en cualquier
broadcast of Telecinco it is forbidden to
emisión de telecinco está prohibido
talk about this subject or that seems to foresee
hablar de este tema o eso parece prever
Carlota Corredera in an interview
a carlota corredera en una entrevista no
had no choice because they asked her
tuvo más remedio porque le preguntaron
context it is a subject that I am not going to go
contexto es un tema en el que no voy a
into because those who had to speak
entrar porque quienes tenían que hablar
are the chain of the producer have already
son la cadena de la productora ya han
spoken okay great I mean it is a subject that you are
hablado vale genial o sea es un tema del
not going to talk about because well who
que no vas a hablar porque bueno quién
has to speak was the producer I
tiene que hablar era la productora no
can't get out of there no longer it will let you not
puedo salirme de ahí no ya no te deja no
because I do not have an opinion but because it
porque no tenga una opinión sino porque
is a judicial and very delicate subject
es un tema judicializado y muy delicado
and hopefully  solve that justice okay
y ojalá se solucione esa justicia vale
Carlota inheritance don't get wet it's not milk there's
carlota herencia no te mojas no es leche
no security no sister this issue not
no hay seguridad no hermana este tema no
because they can kick you out on the [ __ ] street not
porque te pueden echar la calle no
directly musical it's not as you can see there
directamente musical no está como veis
are more than enough reasons to
hay motivos más que de sobra para
throw in your face that your feminism
echarte en cara que tu feminismo
itself is worthless feminism is
mismo no vale para nada el feminismo es
selective and if you don't understand it whenever
selectivo y si no lo entiendes cuando
and wherever you want I will explain it to you
quieras y donde quieras te lo explico
calmly and with respect and I
tranquilamente y desde el respeto y
am also willing to explain to you
también estoy dispuesto a explicarte
forcefully that the presumption of
contundentemente que la presunción de
innocence which is the true feminism
inocencia que es el verdadero feminismo
of feminism and I believe that it should be
del feminismo y yo creo que debería ser
anything but a weapon that serves
cualquier cosa menos un arma que sirva
to attack your enemies your
para atacar a tus enemigos a tu
opponent not whoever you consider your
contrincante no a quien tú consideres tu
opponent with an easy and
contrincante con un argumento fácil e
irrefutable argument much less a business
irrebatible mucho menos un negocio
because in the end what I had done is a
porque al final lo que había hecho es un
business because according to salem the sentence
negocio porque según salem la condena
that antonio david flores won
que os gano antonio david flores
you made an agreement with fidel and
hicisteis un acuerdo con fidel y con
rosito in exchange for the documentary and
rosito a cambio del documental y
withdrew and all the demands that you
retiraba y todas las demandas que
had from them not the
teníais por parte de ellos no las
compensations basically in the first place you
indemnizaciones básicamente en la ida me
are telling me that everything that  You have
estáis diciendo que todo lo que habéis
defended Rocío Carrasco and others, it is
defendido a rocío carrasco y demás es
only a business because if I win, this
solamente un negocio pues si gano está
true selective feminist
verdadera feminista selectiva
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah